A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1946
  - United States, 1946; 1946/200
    - United States - (L-Li), 1946 (Box 329, Folder 2226)
    - United States - (Lo-Ma), 1946 (Box 329, Folder 2227)
    - United States - (Me), 1946 (Box 330, Folder 2228)
    - United States - (Mi-Mz), 1946 (Box 330, Folder 2229)
    - United States - (N-National B), 1946 (Box 330, Folder 2230)
    - United States - National Committee on Atomic Information - (Study Kit) - 1, 1946 (Box 330, Folder 2231)
    - United States - National Committee on Atomic Information - (Correspondence) - 2, 1946 (Box 330, Folder 2232)
    - United States - (National C-I), 1946 (Box 330, Folder 2233)
    - United States - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1946 (Box 331, Folder 2234)
    - United States - (National P-Nz), 1946 (Box 331, Folder 2235)
    - United States - (O-Pe), 1946 (Box 331, Folder 2236)
    - United States - (Pe-Pr), 1946 (Box 331, Folder 2237)
    - United States - Princeton University - Bicentennial Conference, 1946 (Box 331, Folder 2238)
    - United States - (Princeton-Q), 1946 (Box 331, Folder 2239)
    - United States - (Ra-Rh), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2240)
    - United States - (Ri-Ro), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2241)
    - United States - (Ru), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2242)
    - United States - (Sa), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2243)
    - United States - (Sc-Sh), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2244)
    - United States - (She-Sn), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2245)
    - United States - (So-Te), 1946 (Box 332, Folder 2246)
    - United States - (Th-Un), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2247)
    - United States - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2248)
    - United States - (United States: A-O), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2249)
    - United States - (United States: Public Health Service), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2250)
    - United States - (United States: S-Se), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2251)
    - United States - (United States: St-Sz), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2252)
    - United States - (Un-Uz), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2253)
    - United States - (V), 1946 (Box 333, Folder 2254)
    - United States - (W-Wi), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2255)
    - United States - (Wo-Z), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2256)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/200.A
      - United States - (A-S), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2257)
      - United States - (T-Z), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2258)
    - United States - Nursing, 1946; 1946/200.C
      - United States, 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2259)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/200.D
      - United States, 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2259)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/200.E
      - United States - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2260)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (A-D), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2261)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (A-D), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2262)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (A-D), 1946 (Box 334, Folder 2263)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (E-O), 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2264)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (E-O), 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2265)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (E-O), 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2266)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (E-O), 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2267)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (P-Z), 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2268)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (P-Z), 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2269)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1946; 1946/200.L
      - United States, 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2270)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/200.R
      - United States, 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2270)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/200.S
      - United States - Social Science Research Council, 1946 (Box 335, Folder 2271)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2272)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2273)
  - California, 1946; 1946/205
    - California - (A-S), 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2274)
    - California - (University of California), 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2275)
    - California - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/205.A
      - California, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2276)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/205.S
      - California, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2276)
  - Colorado, 1946; 1946/207
    - Colorado, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2277)
    - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/207.S
      - Colorado, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2277)
  - Florida, 1946; 1946/211
    - Florida, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2277)
  - Georgia, 1946; 1946/212
    - Georgia, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2277)
  - Hawaii, 1946; 1946/214
    - Hawaii, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2277)
    - Hawaii - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/214.A
      - Hawaii, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2277)
  - Illinois, 1946; 1946/216
    - Illinois, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2278)
    - Illinois - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/216.A
      - Illinois, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2278)
    - Illinois - Natural Sciences, 1946; 1946/216.D
      - Illinois, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2278)
    - Illinois - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/216.S
      - Illinois, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2278)
  - Indiana, 1946; 1946/217
    - Indiana, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2279)
  - Kansas, 1946; 1946/219
    - Kansas, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2279)
  - Louisiana, 1946; 1946/221
    - Louisiana, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2279)
  - Massachusetts, 1946; 1946/224
    - Massachusetts, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2279)
    - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/224.A
      - Massachusetts, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2279)
  - Michigan, 1946; 1946/225
    - Michigan, 1946 (Box 336, Folder 2279)
  - Mississippi, 1946; 1946/227
    - Mississippi, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2280)
  - Missouri, 1946; 1946/228
    - Missouri, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2280)
  - New Jersey, 1946; 1946/233
    - New Jersey, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2281)
  - New York, 1946; 1946/235
    - New York, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2281)
  - North Carolina, 1946; 1946/236
    - North Carolina, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2281)
  - Ohio, 1946; 1946/238
    - Ohio, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2282)
  - Oregon, 1946; 1946/240
    - Oregon, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2282)
    - Oregon - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/240.R
      - Oregon, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2282)
  - Pennsylvania, 1946; 1946/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2283)
    - Pennsylvania - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/241.A
      - Pennsylvania, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2283)
  - Philippines, 1946; 1946/242
    - Philippines, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2284)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/242.A
      - Philippines, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2285)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 1946; 1946/242.C
      - Philippines, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2285)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/242.E
      - Philippines, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2285)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/242.R
      - Philippines, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2285)
  - Rhode Island, 1946; 1946/244
    - Rhode Island, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2286)
  - South Carolina, 1946; 1946/246
    - South Carolina, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2286)
  - South Dakota, 1946; 1946/247
    - South Dakota, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2286)
  - Tennessee, 1946; 1946/248
    - Tennessee, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2286)
  - Utah, 1946; 1946/250
    - Utah, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2286)
  - Vermont, 1946; 1946/251
    - Vermont, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2286)
  - Virginia, 1946; 1946/252
    - Virginia, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2287)
    - Virginia - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/252.R
      - Virginia, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2287)
  - Washington, 1946; 1946/253
    - Washington, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2287)
  - Wisconsin, 1946; 1946/255
    - Wisconsin, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2287)
  - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands, 1946; 1946/258
    - Pacific Islands Trust, 1946 (Box 337, Folder 2287)
  - South America, 1946; 1946/300
    - South America - Administration, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2288)
    - South America - Administration, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2289)
    - South America - Administration, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2290)
    - South America, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2291)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/300.A
      - South America, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2291)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/300.E
      - South America, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2291)
  - Argentina, 1946; 1946/301
    - Argentina - (A-L), 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2292)
    - Argentina - (M-Z), 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2293)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/301.A
      - Argentina, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2293)
  - Bolivia, 1946; 1946/303
    - Bolivia, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2294)
    - Bolivia - Nursing, 1946; 1946/303.C
      - Bolivia, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2294)
  - Brazil, 1946; 1946/305
    - Brazil, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2295)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/305.D
      - Brazil, 1946 (Box 338, Folder 2295)
  - Chile, 1946; 1946/309
    - Chile, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2296)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1946; 1946/309.C
      - Chile, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2296)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/309.E
      - Chile, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2296)
  - Colombia, 1946; 1946/311
    - Colombia, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2297)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/311.D
      - Colombia, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2297)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/311.E
      - Colombia, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2297)
  - Costa Rica, 1946; 1946/313
    - Costa Rica, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
  - Cuba, 1946; 1946/315
    - Cuba, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
  - Ecuador, 1946; 1946/317
    - Ecuador, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
    - Ecuador - Malaria, 1946; 1946/317.I
      - Ecuador, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
  - Guatemala, 1946; 1946/319
    - Guatemala, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
    - Guatemala - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/319.S
      - Guatemala, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
  - Honduras, 1946; 1946/321
    - Honduras, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2298)
  - Mexico, 1946; 1946/323
    - Mexico - Administration - (A-M), 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2299)
    - Mexico - Mexican - American Agricultural Commission, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2300)
    - Mexico - (M-Z), 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2301)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/323.D
      - Mexico, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2301)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/323.R
      - Mexico, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2301)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/323.S
      - Mexico, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2301)
  - Nicaragua, 1946; 1946/325
    - Nicaragua, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2302)
  - Panama, 1946; 1946/327
    - Panama, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2302)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/327.E
      - Panama, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2302)
  - Paraguay, 1946; 1946/329
    - Paraguay, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2302)
    - Paraguay - Malaria, 1946; 1946/329.I
      - Paraguay, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2302)
    - Paraguay - Yellow Fever, 1946; 1946/329.O
      - Paraguay, 1946 (Box 339, Folder 2302)
  - Peru, 1946; 1946/331
    - Peru, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2303)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/331.A
      - Peru, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2303)
    - Peru - Nursing, 1946; 1946/331.C
      - Peru, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2303)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/331.E
      - Peru, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2303)
  - El Salvador, 1946; 1946/333
    - El Salvador, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2304)
  - Dominican Republic, 1946; 1946/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2304)
    - Dominican Republic - Nursing, 1946; 1946/335.C
      - Dominican Republic, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2304)
  - Uruguay, 1946; 1946/337
    - Uruguay, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2304)
    - Uruguay - Nursing, 1946; 1946/337.C
      - Uruguay, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2304)
    - Uruguay - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/337.R
      - Uruguay, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2304)
  - Venezuela, 1946; 1946/339
    - Venezuela - (A-R), 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2305)
    - Venezuela - (S-Z), 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2306)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2306)
  - Great Britain, 1946; 1946/400
    - Great Britian, 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2307)
  - England, 1946; 1946/401
    - England - (A-F), 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2307)
    - England - (G-Ma), 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2308)
    - England - (Me-Pe), 1946 (Box 340, Folder 2309)
    - England - (R-Z), 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2310)
    - England - (R-Z), 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2311)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/401.A
      - England, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2312)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/401.E
      - England, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2312)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/401.R
      - England, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2312)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/401.S
      - England, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2312)
  - Ireland, 1946; 1946/403
    - Ireland, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2313)
    - Ireland - Nursing, 1946; 1946/403.C
      - Ireland, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2313)
  - Scotland, 1946; 1946/405
    - Scotland, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2313)
    - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/405.S
      - Scotland, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2313)
  - Wales, 1946; 1946/409
    - Wales, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2313)
  - Australia, 1946; 1946/410
    - Australia, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/410.A
      - Australia, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/410.E
      - Australia, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/410.R
      - Australia, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
  - New Zealand, 1946; 1946/418
    - New Zealand, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
  - Fiji, 1946; 1946/419
    - Fiji - Nursing, 1946; 1946/419.C
      - Fiji, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2314)
  - Caribbean Region, 1946; 1946/420
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1946 (Box 341, Folder 2315)
  - Guyana, 1946; 1946/423
    - Guiana, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2316)
  - Honduras, 1946; 1946/425
    - Honduras, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2316)
  - Canada, 1946; 1946/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2317)
    - Canada - British Columbia - Health, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2318)
    - Canada - British Columbia - Health, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2319)
    - Canada - Health, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2320)
    - Canada - Manitoba Health Survey - 1, 1946 (Box 342, Folder 2321)
    - Canada - Manitoba Health Survey - 2, 1946 (Box 343, Folder 2322)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 343, Folder 2323)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 343, Folder 2324)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 343, Folder 2325)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/427.A
      - Canada - University of British Columbia Medical School - 1-2, 1946 (Box 343, Folder 2326)
      - Canada - University of British Columbia Medical School - 1-2, 1946 (Box 343, Folder 2327)
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2328)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1946; 1946/427.C
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2328)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1946; 1946/427.D
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2328)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/427.E
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2328)
    - Canada - Declinations, 1946; 1946/427.F
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2328)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1946; 1946/427.L
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2328)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/427.R
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2329)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/427.S
      - Canada, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2330)
  - St. Lucia, 1946; 1946/431
    - St. Lucia, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - Bahamas, 1946; 1946/433
    - Bahamas, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - Barbados, 1946; 1946/435
    - Barbados, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - Jamaica, 1946; 1946/437
    - Jamaica, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/437.A
      - Jamaica, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - Trinidad, 1946; 1946/451
    - Trinidad, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - Windward Islands, 1946; 1946/455
    - Windward Islands, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - Ceylon, 1946; 1946/462
    Sri Lanka
    - Ceylon - Malaria, 1946; 1946/462.I
      - Ceylon, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2331)
  - India, 1946; 1946/464
    - India - Administration, 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2332)
    - India - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2333)
    - India - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 344, Folder 2334)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/464.A
      - India, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2335)
    - India - Nursing, 1946; 1946/464.C
      - India, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2335)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/464.E
      - India, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2335)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1946; 1946/464.L
      - India, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2335)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1946; 1946/464.O
      - India, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2335)
  - Burma, 1946; 1946/468
    Myanmar
    - Burma, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2336)
  - Malaysia, 1946; 1946/473
    Malaysia
    - Malaysia, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2336)
  - Africa, 1946; 1946/475
    - Africa, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2336)
  - East Africa Region, 1946; 1946/477
    - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/477.A
      - East Africa, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2336)
  - North Africa Region, 1946; 1946/485
    - Egypt - Administration - (A-H), 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2337)
    - Egypt - (I-Z), 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2338)
    - North Africa Region - Nursing, 1946; 1946/485.C
      - Egypt, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2338)
    - North Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/485.E
      - Egypt, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2338)
  - South Africa Region, 1946; 1946/487
    - South Africa, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2339)
    - South Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/487.A
      - South Africa, 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2339)
  - France, 1946; 1946/500
    - France - (A-G), 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2340)
    - France - (A-G), 1946 (Box 345, Folder 2341)
    - France - (H-Z), 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2342)
    - France - (H-Z), 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2343)
    - France - (H-Z), 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2344)
    - France - Medical Scienes, 1946; 1946/500.A
      - France, 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2345)
    - France - Nursing, 1946; 1946/500.C
      - France, 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2345)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/500.E
      - France, 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2345)
      - France - Government Fellowships - (A-M), 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2346)
      - France - Government Fellowships - (A-M), 1946 (Box 346, Folder 2347)
      - France - Government Fellowships - (R-Z), 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2348)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/500.R
      - France, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2349)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/500.S
      - France, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2349)
  - French Guiana, 1946; 1946/507
    French Guiana
    - French Guiana, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2350)
  - Vietnam, 1946; 1946/509
    - Vietnam, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2350)
  - Asia, 1946; 1946/600
    - Asia - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/600.A
      - Asia, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2350)
    - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/600.R
      - Asia, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2350)
  - China, 1946; 1946/601
    - China - Administration, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2351)
    - China - Administration - Commutation, 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2352)
    - China - (A-H), 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2353)
    - China - (A-H), 1946 (Box 347, Folder 2354)
    - China - (I-P), 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2355)
    - China - (Peiking Union Medical College), 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2356)
    - China - (S-Z), 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2357)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/601.A
      - China, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2358)
    - China - Nursing, 1946; 1946/601.C
      - China, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2358)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/601.E
      - China, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2358)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/601.R
      - China, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2358)
    - China - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/601.S
      - China, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2358)
  - Taiwan, 1946; 1946/605
    Taiwan
    - Taiwan - Nursing, 1946; 1946/605.C
      - Taiwan, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
  - Japan, 1946; 1946/609
    - Japan, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/609.E
      - Japan, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
  - Korea, 1946; 1946/613
    - Korea, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
    - Korea - Nursing, 1946; 02.1946/613.C
      - Korea, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
  - Thailand, 1946; 1946/617
    - Thailand, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/617.A
      - Thailand, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2359)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1946; 1946/650
    - Netherlands - (A-St), 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2360)
    - Netherlands - Student Health Service, 1946 (Box 348, Folder 2361)
    - Netherlands - (T-Z), 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2362)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/650.A
      - Netherlands, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2363)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2363)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Health Services, 1946; 1946/650.K
      - Netherlands, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2363)
      - LOG-1 Logan, John A. "A Preliminary Report on the Sanitary Engineering Situation in Holland", 1946 (Box 562, Folder 3831A)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2363)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2363)
  - Java, 1946; 1946/655
    - Java, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2363)
  - Europe, 1946; 1946/700
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/700.S
      - Europe, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2364)
  - Ethiopia, 1946; 1946/701
    - Ethiopia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2364)
  - Austria, 1946; 1946/705
    - Austria, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2364)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/705.A
      - Austria, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2364)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/705.E
      - Austria, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2364)
  - Balkan Region, 1946; 1946/706
    Balkan Peninsula
    - Balkan Region, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2364)
  - Belgium, 1946; 1946/707
    - Belgium, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2365)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1946; 1946/707.R
      - Belgium, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2365)
    - Belgium - Tuberculosis, 1946; 1946/707.T
      - Belgium, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2365)
  - Zaire, 1946; 1946/709
    - Congo (Zaire), 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2366)
  - Yugoslavia, 1946; 1946/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2366)
    - Yugoslavia - Nursing, 1946; 1946/710.C
      - Yugoslavia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2366)
  - Bulgaria, 1946; 1946/711
    - Bulgaria, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2366)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1946; 1946/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2367)
    - Czechoslovakia - Medical Sciences, 1946; 1946/712.A
      - Czechoslovakia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2367)
    - Czechoslovakia - Nursing, 1946; 1946/712.C
      - Czechoslovakia, 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2367)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1946; 1946/712.E